dailyme.com 2017-12-28

# Corporates

DailyMe, Inc., a Delaware corporation ("DailyMe") is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. Please read the following policy to understand how your personally identifiable information will be treated as you make use of our current offerings. DailyMe has created this Privacy Policy in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses how we gather information from users, and others who visit the DailyMe website, our information dissemination practices and the information services therein. 

Our Privacy Policy will let you know:

  * What do we track?
  * What we do with the information we gather?
  * Our opt-out policy
  * Changing or modifying your Personally Identifiable Information
  * What security precautions are in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of my information?
  * Children's policy
  * Contact information
  * Ad network opt-out links

This privacy policy is incorporated into and is subject to the DailyMe Terms of Service. Your use of the DailyMe website and any personally identifiable information you provide on the DailyMe Sites remains subject to the terms of this privacy policy and the DailyMe Terms of Service. By using the DailyMe website you accept and agree to be bound by the terms of this privacy policy.

Any content, including text, images and/or video posted at the decision of the user onto the DailyMe website becomes published content and is not considered personally identifiable information subject to this privacy policy.

This policy does not cover any interaction you may have with DailyMe by telephone, postal mail, or other offline communications.

This policy may change from time to time and DailyMe is under no obligation to inform you of any such changes, so please check back periodically to ensure your continued acceptance of such privacy policy. 

This DailyMe Privacy Policy was last updated on December 21, 2006. 

### What do we track?

DailyMe website's registration form requires you to provide us with personally identifiable information including certain mandatory contact information (including your name, and email address), and certain additional optional demographic information (like your zip code), and your content preferences in order to provide you with the DailyMe service. DailyMe retains this information for our use only. We use customer contact information and professional interest information from the registration form to generate and send the DailyMe containing content based on your account and profile. We also use this contact information to send email announcements about our company and products, to contact you if there are any changes to the website that will affect your user experience, and to send out surveys for our own information. On occasions, we also use this information on behalf of our advertisers or partners. You may opt-out of receiving future mailings; please review our opt-out policy below. 

Demographic and profile data is also collected at our website. We use this data to tailor the visitor's experience at our website, showing you content that we think you might be interested in, and displaying the content according to your preferences. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis, but not individually. 

Our website may use cookies and may adopt other tracking methods to keep track of your DailyMe experience, to avoid displaying the same ads repeatedly, to improve the user experience. We may use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our website. Users of DailyMe always have the option of disabling cookies via their browser preferences. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by us and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

DailyMe also collects IP addresses for system administration and to report aggregate non-personally identifiable information to our advertisers. 

We may allow other companies, called ad networks, to serve advertisements to the users of our website. Ad networks include third party ad servers, ad agencies, ad technology vendors, and research firms. DailyMe may "target" some ads to users that fit a certain general profile, for example, "product managers in Florida." To deliver these ads properly, DailyMe may include a file, called a web "beacon" or a "clear GIF", from these ad networks within pages served by DailyMe so the networks may provide anonymized (without using personally identifiable information), aggregated auditing, research, and reporting for advertisers as well as to target ads to you while you visit other websites. Web beacons are used to track our users anonymously and to determine which emails we send to our users are opened by the recipients. 

Because your web browser must request these advertisements and web beacons from the ad network's servers, these companies can view, edit, or set their own cookies, just as if you had requested a web page from their website. 

These general targets may also be used by ad networks to display targeted ads on other websites as a substitute for random, irrelevant ads. 

You may opt-out of use of web beacons in the pages of our website that you view and of placement of a cookie by ad networks in your browser. If you opt-out you will lose the potential benefit of receiving ads that are more targeted to your interests. 

Our website contains links to other websites. By clicking on any of these links, you acknowledge that we are not responsible for the content of such links. Moreover these websites' privacy policies may differ from this privacy policy. We strongly encourage you to read the privacy policy of any website you may visit. 

It is your responsibility to maintain the confidentiality of your account information. We advise that you should be cautious about posting a real e-mail address, your actual name or other personally identifiable information to your Profile Page and other areas of our website, including blogs newsgroups, chat groups, or other public forums. 

From time to time, we or a partner may sponsor a promotion, sweepstake or contest on our website. You may be asked to provide personally identifiable information including name, email address or home address or to answer questions in order to participate. We may transfer personally identifiable information to certain ad partners that you have explicitly requested to receive information from. It will be clear at the point of collection who is collecting the personally identifiable information and whose privacy statement will apply. 

### What we do with the information we gather 

We are continually striving to make DailyMe a better news and information website for you. In order to accomplish it, we continually monitor and analyze the aggregate information we collect on our users. 

We analyze the traffic patterns throughout DailyMe to highlight popular areas, and improve those sections which are not meeting the needs of our users. 

We share non-personally identifiable aggregate information with our advertisers concerning our users and their interests. An example of this type of information might be "20% of the people who clicked on Advertisement X have a telecommunications-related topic in their individual news profile." 

We use customer contact information and professional interest information from the registration form to send the DailyMe Digest containing headline news and/or stories based on a your personal profile. We also use this contact information to send email announcements about our company and products, to contact you if there are any changes to the website that will affect your user experience, and to send out surveys for our own information. On occasions, we also use this information on behalf of our advertisers or partners. You may opt-out of receiving future mailings; please review our Opt-out Policy below. 

Except as otherwise described in this policy, we will not disclose personally identifiable information and non-personally identifiable information to any third party unless we believe that disclosure is necessary: (1) to conform to legal requirements or to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other legal process received by us, whether or not a response is required by applicable law; (2) to enforce the our Terms of Service or to protect our rights; or (3) to protect the safety of members of the public and users of the service. We reserve the right to transfer personally identifiable information to a successor in interest that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale of DailyMe or substantially all of its assets to that successor in interest. 

Any personally identifiable information or content that you voluntarily disclose online (on discussion boards, in messages and chat areas) becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others. 

### Our opt-out policy 

DailyMe provides you with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving any communications from us. 

You have the opportunity to "opt-out" of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes, including marketing purposes, when we ask for this information. For example, if you no longer wish to receive promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each communication or by modifying your personally identifiable information to indicate such preference at any time by clicking on your Profile Page section of DailyMe. 

If you wish to opt out of the collection and analysis of the stories you read for the purpose of making more precise story recommendations, you may do so by clicking on this link and following the instructions on the **My Newstogram page**.

### Changing or modifying your personally identifiable information 

You may update or modify your personally identifiable information at any time by clicking on your Profile Page section of DailyMe 

### What security precautions are in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of my information? 

DailyMe operates secure data networks protected by industry standard firewall and password protection systems. Our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary and only authorized individuals have access to the information provided by our customers. 

### Children's policy 

Registration on our website is not available to anyone under the age of 13. We do not intend to collect information from persons under the age of 13. We ask that anyone under these ages not register on our website and not to submit any personally identifiable information through our website. We do not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under these ages. 

### Contact information 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of the DailyMe website, or your dealings with the DailyMe website, please contact us by sending an email message to **legal@dailyme.com** or by writing to the following address: 

DailyMe, Inc.,  
Attention: General Counsel  
4000 Hollywood Blvd. Suite # 745-S   
Hollywood, FL 33021. 

### AD NETWORK OPT-OUT LINKS 

To opt-out of use of web beacons and of placement of a cookie by ad networks used on DailyMe, please visit the following sites:
